CUONG NGUYEN

College Student

ckn006@bucknell.edu www.cuongnguyen.me

INTRODUCTION -

Hi, I'm Cuong. As a Computer Science and Design Art student with diverse experience across multiple roles, I have developed a unique set of multidisciplinary skills that allow me to bring a fresh perspective and innovative solutions to complex challenges. I have had my fair share of experience working at a consumer-facing startup as a UX designer. Being the sole design generalist, I punched through all design problems and delivered presentations to higher seniors. Throughout my time at Bucknell, I have taken up multiple responsibilities, from being a software developer to a Scrum Master; therefore, I can sympathize with and understand the design handoff fully. My time working as a Full Stack Developer showed that I'm comfortable with exploring incertitude and learning new skill sets by myself. My experience with HCI involved a data visualization project where, through Tableau, we analyzed how data can convey both informative and manipulative patterns. Fresh off college, I will step up and reach my goal of becoming a global designer and leader, bringing my expertise to help and mentor people.

WORK EXPERIENCE -

Software Engineer

Bucknell University, PA, USA (06/2021 - Present)

- Renovated and developed a new user experience for the <u>Ready Set Fit</u> mobile app, resulting in a 77% increase in app impressions and a 175% increase in product page views (App Store).
- Led the development of wireframes, prototypes, and high-fidelity designs using industry-standard tools such as Figma and Adobe Creative Suite, producing a successful fitness program that garnered increased public engagement from community partners.

UX Designer

Alobase Technology and Services JSC, Hanoi, Vietnam (08/2020 - 04/2021)

- Led the product design process of 2 B2B SAAS projects, including <u>Trekkrs</u>, a community platform for startups to connect with VCs. Successfully achieved MVP versions within 4 months each.
- Promoted collaboration and consistency across teams, including an outsourcing agency, through effective communication and design hand-off.
- Facilitated meetings with development team, higher seniors, and clients to deliver design presentation and project goals.
- Managed the media design team for a major company-hosted event and successfully promoted it to reach an international audience of 3000 college students, 23 leading corporations, and 154 investment funds.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE AND AWARDS —

Google UX Design Certificate 09/2022

Innovation Award for BizPitch – Bucknell's Entrepreneur Competition

Bucknell University (04/2022)

EDUCATION —

Bucknell University PA, USA (08/2019 - 05/2023)

- Bachelor of Arts in **Computer Science**
- Minor in Art Studio Design

Current GPA: 3.79 /4.0 Related coursework:

- Software Engineer and Design
- Mobile Computing
- Web Design
- Human-Computer Interaction
- Accessibility
- Social Psychology

SKILLS —

Software

Figma Webflow

Adobe Suites Unreal Engine

Blender Tableau

Specialized Skills

UI, UX Graphic Design

User Research Android, IOS

Prototyping HTML, CSS

Usability Test ReactJS

LEADERSHIP —

VP of Communication for Vietnamese Student Association

03/2020 - 05/2022

- Designed and created graphic materials and media to effectively promote the club to local students.
- Co-organized and led 10+ club activities and events, ensuring effective public relations and communication at the university level.

LET'S CONNECT —

linkedin.com/in/cuongnguyen27 dribbble.com/ckuong github.com/nkcuong2761